[{"answer": "Yeah, they showed m", "docId": "mulholland_drive.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Could be...any of those dead kids wearin' pearl earrings", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Could be unrelated", "docId": "mulholland_drive.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "No. Could be someone's missin' maybe", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "To my friend's? I wasn't going to say anything, but why my friend's", "docId": "mulholland_drive.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Okay. Why this my friend's", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I guess it was your grandfather, was it ... he called me to check in, said you were on your way and for you to call when you get in. Nice man... farmer I hear", "docId": "mulholland_drive.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Damn lot of corn raised in that place these days too", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "my friend...you better take care of this", "docId": "mulholland_drive.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Hold on!!!!!!!! There's no way, there's no way!!", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Well...  what do you think about then? I mean...  well what do you think about", "docId": "mulholland_drive.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Well ... if you don't remember anything, I mean what goes through your mind then if you don't remember anything", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Nothing. I do remember the car crash... I told you... I remember the glass ... I think about that sometimes ... I remember walking here, sort of. Now I remember this place and you. That's about it", "docId": "mulholland_drive.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "I don't know", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "How do you remember how to talk", "docId": "mulholland_drive.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "You don't remember anything else", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "What did you say", "docId": "mulholland_drive.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Who fired everyone", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "that place", "docId": "mulholland_drive.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "That's where I was going... Mulholland Drive", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": " Come on. It'll be just like in the movies. We'll pretend to be someone else. I want to walk around anyway. I'm in that place and I haven't even seen any of it. Come on my friend. Do you feel up to it", "docId": "mulholland_drive.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Just to see if there was an accident on that place", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": " Yes? May I help you", "docId": "mulholland_drive.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "my friend's gone on a film. I'm her niece my friend.   Who are you", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Unbelievable. Look... here.  I don't know what's going on. That's so much baloney. I've got enough cash for one night, okay", "docId": "mulholland_drive.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Fine. I'll check out in the morning", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "And", "docId": "mulholland_drive.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "But I'm not broke", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "The Cowboy?", "docId": "mulholland_drive.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Oh, my friend thought it would be a good idea for me to meet the Cowboy. Should I wear my ten gallon hat and my six shooters", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Now... did you answer cause you thought that's what I wanted to hear or did you think about what I said and answer cause you truly believe that to be right", "docId": "mulholland_drive.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "What did I say", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Why didn't you ask him? Sol knows you", "docId": "mulholland_drive.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "You're not going to get in trouble. You're going to find out who you are. Finding out who you are gets you out of trouble", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "my friend... I know what you're doing", "docId": "mulholland_drive.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "I know what you have to do, but let me do it", "qsentId": 36}]